# **Carlos Sarante**

# Full Stack Web Developer - Conuco Agencia Creativa

Peekskill, NY - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Carlos-Sarante/8626bf6e19d3e6ac

Web Developer with 3+ years building and maintaining web applications for client side and server side as well. Proficient in technologies such as, Javascript, Python and many other frameworks and technologies. Always looking to deliver a fast and a good quality solution.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Full Stack Web Developer**

Conuco Agencia Creativa - 2013 to Present

Located in Santiago, Dominican Republic, Conuco is always seeking to give to its clients an identity and improve its digital presence on the World Wide Web and social media platforms.

#### Tasks

- Creating and maintaining themes for Wordpress pages.
- Backend Development using Django framework, Python and PHP (for Wordpress).
- Configuring web server for all pages (NGINX).
- Fixing hosting server issues.

# **Web Developer**

Intellisys DCorp - Santiago de Chile, Región Metropolitana - May 2015 to May 2017

## Web Developer

Condé Nast - 2015 to 2017

Create different ad and subscription tools to accomplish the user engagement for all brands from Condé Nast.

## Tasks

- Creating ads markups (HTML/CSS) for use in Doubleclick Publisher platform.
- Create new failsafe ad units for different magazine brands from this editorial.
- Creating a tool to make the process of ad creation easier for not so experienced developers, using pre-designed templates.
- Fixing style and functionality bugs for the different ad units.

# Web Developer

The New Book Press - 2015 to 2016

The mission for Wordplay Shakespeare was to make a better user experience involving the speed of the site and integrating new language tools.

#### Tasks

- Perform migration to Open EdX platform.
- Migration to use Mongoose framework as the current ODM for MongoDB.
- Update Express Framework views from 3.x to 4.x.

• Implementing new features for the user administration system and media content.

# **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor's in Telematics Engineer**

Pontificia Universidad Católica Madre y Maestra - Santiago de Chile, Región Metropolitana September 2007 to January 2013

## **SKILLS**

C# (Less than 1 year), Django (4 years), MongoDB. (1 year), NGINX (4 years), Python (4 years)

## **LINKS**

https://www.linkedin.com/in/carlos-manuel-sarante-p%C3%A9rez-b046bb62

### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Current Skillset

- Server Side: Node.JS, Python, MySQL, MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, Django, NGINX Configuration.
- Client Side: React JS, Angular 1.x, jQuery, CSS3, HTML5.
- Language Knowledge: Javascript, Python and C#.
- Other Technologies: Git, Webpack and Wordpress (Theme Development).